hello guys welcome to my YouTube Channel
Please Subscribe my channel and press
the Bell
icon if you like our video please like
and share our video in this video we are
telling about what is the health
insurance it definitions and how it work
what is the health insurance first of
all the introduction about the health
insurance
health insurance is a contract between a
company and a consumer the company agree
to pay all of or some of the insured
person health care cost in term for the
payment of a monthly premium the
contract is usually a onee agreement
during which the insurer will be
responsible for paying fix expenses
related to the illness injury pregnancy
or preventative
carrier health insurance agreements in
the USA generally came with the
expectations or to coverage
including a deductable that required the
consumer to pay certain health care cost
out of the procket up to the maximum
amount before the company coverages
begin one or more Co payments that
required that consumer to pay a set
share of the the cost for the specific
Services of the
producer health insurance pay most
medical and surgical expenses and
preventative care cost insured by the
insured person in return for the monthly
premium payment generally the higher the
monthly premium is the lower the out of
the pocket cost are to the
insured rightfully all insurance plans
have detectable and copay but the out of
the pocket expenses are now CED for the
federal law since 2010 the Affordable
Care Act has prohibited insurance
company from denying coverages to
patient with the
prefixing conditions and has allow
children to remain on their parents
insurance plan until they reach the age
of
26 Medical Care medicated and the
children health insurance programs are
the federal health insurance plan that
extend coverages to the older disabled
and lowincome
people how does it work in the United
States health insurance is trickly to
navigate it is the business when the
number of the regional and the national
competitors who coverages PR pricing and
availability very for the state to state
and even by a country about half of the
population has the health insurance
coverages as the employment benefits
with the premium partic coverages by the
employer the cost of the employer is tax
deductable to the payer and benefits to
the companies are the tax fee which
certain expectations for the as
cooperator Employer s self employer
people Freelancers and the gig Works can
buy insurance directly on their own the
affordable act care of the 2010 commonly
called many dates there are certains of
the nation debits called healthcare.
government which allow individual to
search for their standard plans for
their private insurance that are
available where they live the cost of
the coverages are the used for the
taxpayer who is income or the 10% and
400% for the federal property throw
hard type of the health
insurance so-called manage care
insurance plan required policy holder to
get their carrier for a network to
designed the health care provider it
patient seek out care the network the
must pay a higher percentage of the cost
the insurance may even refuse the
payment outright for the services obtain
out of the network many manage care plan
for example Health maintenance
organization and point of the services
plan required the patient to choose a
primary care physician Who overseas the
patients care make the recommendations
about the treatment